# CONTACT

# GIOVANNI COAKLEY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PHONE: 1.416.997.8177

EMAIL: gcoakley.jr@gmail.com

WEBSITE: gioco.netlify.app

GITHUB: github.com/gcoakleyjr

Toronto, ON

Canada



#### **ABOUT**

Experienced Developer and Technical Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the architecture, planning, and design industry. Skilled in Web Development, Design, and 3D Visualization. Strong arts and design professional with a Bachelor of Architecture - BArch focused in Architecture from Louisiana State University.

#### SKILLS

#### Web Development

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript

MERN (MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, React, Node.js)

Git, Heroku

3D

Three.js, Blender, Sketchup, 3D Modeling and Visualization

## Software

Visual Studio Code, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Premeire

#### REFERENCE

#### **MAY JULSUWAN**

Project Manager - Gensler may.julsuwan@gmail.com linkedin

#### **BRYAN SOUTHWICK**

Project Manager - Gensler bsouthwi@gmail.com linkedin

#### RECENT PROJECTS

#### Kijiji Rental Mapper

kijijimapper.herokuapp.com git

A fullstack application developed using React.js and Material UI for a high-fidelity UX/UI design and Node.js and Express.js server to create an API used to fetch rental information for a client.

#### **Toronto Social App**

mapto.herokuapp.com git

A MERN stack application focused on using MongoDB and Mogoose ODM for storing user generated data, and then displayed on a map of Toronto. Utlizes Passport for user authentication, alogorithims for trending posts, and EJS for displaying all of the data.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **GENSLER**

SEPT 2018 - PRESENT

**Technical Designer** 

Collaborated on a daily basis with team members, contractors and clients to design and build commercial architectural projects throughout North America. Responsibilities include teaching new hires modeling softwares, interior and exterior design, visualization, diagram and graphic design, client presentations, spatial planning, and documentation.

#### **HOFFPAUIR STUDIO**

MAY 2018 - AUG 2018

Architectural Designer

Design and visualization of projects in Louisiana, US, ranging from office rooftop terrace to a community church masterplan.

#### **EDUCATION**

# LOUISIANA STATE UNIVERSITY

AUG 2013 - MAY 2018

Bachelor of Architecture, Professional Degree